http://www.beautyschool.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
Terms of use is here: http://www.beautyschool.com/terms-of-useLast updated: March 11, 2019
Your privacy is important to Thruline Marketing, Inc., and its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively referred to as “Thruline,” “us,” “our,” or “we”). We have published this Privacy Policy so you know how we collect, use, and share your personal information.
This Privacy Policy applies our website located at www.thru-line.com and any other website, blog, page, section, or feature that links to this Agreement (collectively, the “Site”), our mobile application (the “App”), and all related services, software, or features (the Services together with the App, collectively, the “Services”).
We may revise and update this Privacy Policy from time to time and will post the updated Privacy Policy to the Services. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy for any updates or changes. UNLESS OTHERWISE INDICATED, ANY CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY WILL APPLY IMMEDIATELY UPON POSTING TO THE SERVICES.
1. YOUR INFORMATION
a. Personal Information You Give Us
Personal information is data that can be used to identify or contact a single person. We collect and may transmit personal information that you provide to us through the Services (“Your Information”). We collect Your Information only if you manually enter it into a form or field on the Services. Your Information includes, but is not limited to, your name, email address, street address, telephone number, gender, age, educational background, and educational interests. You can use the Services without providing Your Information. If you choose not to provide Your Information, you may not be able to use certain services offered on the Services.
b. Information We Collect Automatically
Whenever you interact with the Services (whether via a browser, an application, or otherwise), we automatically receive and record information from your browser. Other information collected automatically may include your IP address, the type of browser or application you are using to access the Services, and the identity of the Services page or feature you are requesting. We may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Services, and gather broad demographic data for aggregate use. We may also collect information regarding the device(s) you use to access or use the Services.
To collect this information, we may use “cookies” or other tracking technologies to track how you use the Services. We also may send instructions to your computer or device using JavaScript or other computer languages to gather the sorts of information described above and other details about your interactions with the Services. A cookie is a file stored on your computer or device to uniquely identify your browser or to store information or settings on your computer or device. If applicable, our advertising partners may also transmit cookies to your browser, application, or mobile device when you click on ads that appear on the Services. Clicking on a link to a third party website from the Services may also allow that third party website to also transmit cookies to you.
We may use cookies that are session-based or persistent. Session cookies exist only during one session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser software or turn off your computer. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you close your browser or turn off your computer.
All modern browsers allow you to change your cookie settings. You can usually find these settings in the Options or Preferences menu of your browser. To understand these settings, the following links may be helpful, or you can use the Help option in your browser for more details.
Cookie settings in Internet Explorer
Cookie settings in Firefox
Cookie settings in Chrome
Cookie settings in Safari web and iOS.
If you are primarily concerned about third party cookies generated by advertisers, you can turn these off by going to the Your Online Choices or by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative’s Opt-out page, where you can control third-party online advertising.  Please note that there are many more networks listed on this site than those that we use on our site. If you would like to find out more about cookies and their use on the Internet, you may find the following links useful:
Microsoft Cookies guide
All About Cookies
Please note that if you disable your web browser’s ability to accept cookies, you will be able to navigate the Services, but you may not be able to successfully use all of the features of the Services.
We use Google Analytics to help us analyze the traffic on the Services. For more information on Google Analytics’ processing of Personal Information, please see “How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps” (https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).
We may also use “web beacons”, i.e. “web bugs” or “single–pixel” or “clear” GIFs, on the Services. Web beacons allow ad networks to provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research, and reporting for us and for advertisers. Web beacons also enable ad networks to serve targeted advertisements to you when you visit other websites. Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network’s servers, these companies can view, edit, or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their website.
Be sure to review the privacy policy of any third party website you visit because this Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies or web beacons by any third parties.
2. HOW WE USE AND DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION
a. Non-Personal Information
We may use and share non-personal, de-identified information (i.e. information that cannot be used to identify you) for any lawful business purpose without any obligation or accounting to you. For example, we can use non-personal information for developing products, services, and providing those offerings to other users and third parties. We may use your personal information to generate non-personal information (e.g., by statistically aggregating your personal information with the information of others). When we do so, we will take reasonable measures to ensure that the non-personal information is no longer personally identifiable and cannot later be used to identify you. We may also disclose non-personal, aggregate, anonymous data in a de-identified format to investors and potential partners based on information collected from users.
b. Personal Information
We may use Your Information in the following ways:
Your Information may be passed on to schools you have selected and agreed to be contacted by, sometimes through a third party who then passes it on to the schools. If the form you filled out was hosted as a part of the Services, we may also send you a confirmation email to acknowledge your activity on the Services.
The schools or their partners or vendors may contact you via email, telephone, or mail in order to fulfill your inquiry. By using the Services to send Your Information to any schools, you are giving such entities permission to contact you, regardless of whether you are a part of the National-Do-Not-Call Registry.
We will store Your Information in our systems and we may use it to contact you about other products or services which we believe may interest you. If we contact you at all in this manner, it will be infrequent and narrowly targeted.
3. OTHER USES OF YOUR INFORMATION
In addition to the uses described above, there are limited circumstances in which we may share Your Information with certain third parties. We may combine Your Information with information we obtain from third party sources, either online or offline, in order to deepen our understanding of how best to serve you with the Services. We may share Your Information with our subsidiaries or affiliates. Your Information may be included among transferred assets in the event that we are involved in a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event. Finally, we may disclose Your Information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend our rights or property, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Services or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability.
4. E-MAIL COMMUNICATIONS
The e-mail address you provide during the Services registration process will be the e-mail address we will use for all Site-related communications to you. We may also send you messages via the Services. The Services may contain links or forms that can be used to contact us so you can comment, make a complaint, make suggestions, and ask questions.
If you subscribe to our email newsletter, but subsequently decide that you would like to stop receiving it, you may use the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each newsletter, or you may contact us at privacy@thru-line.com and we will see to it that your name is removed from our email newsletter list.
5. PROTECTION OF YOUR INFORMATION
Protecting your account login credentials (i.e. your username and password) from unauthorized access is your responsibility. You may not share your login credentials with any third party. We recommend you log out after accessing your account, change your password on a periodic basis, and limit access to your computer or device and its browser. While we use commercially reasonable security measures to prevent unauthorized persons from accessing our files or tampering with the Services, we cannot guarantee that these efforts will always be successful. Your Information may be accessed and viewed by other Internet users, without your knowledge and permission, while in transit to or from us. We cannot and do not guarantee the total privacy or security of any information you transmit through the Services.
6. RETENTION OF YOUR INFORMATION; MODIFICATION
a. Correcting, Updating, Accessing, or Removing Your Information
You can correct, update, or remove Your Information if it changes or if you no longer want to receive information from us beyond information related to our services. This can be done by emailing a request to us at privacy@thru-line.com. You may also request access to Your Information collected by us by sending a request to us at privacy@thru-line.com. We may not be able to completely remove Your Information from our systems in certain circumstances. For example, we may retain Your Information for legitimate business purposes, our customer requirements, or if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, for account recovery purposes, if required by law, or as retained in our data backup systems or cached or archived pages. All of Your Information that we keep will continue to be subject to the terms of the Privacy Policy.
b. Your California Privacy Rights
California law permits users that are residents of California to request the following information regarding our disclosure of Your information to third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes (i) a list of certain categories of Your Information that we have disclosed to certain third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year; (ii) the identity of certain third parties that received Your Information from us for their direct marketing purposes during that calendar year; and (iii) examples of the products or services marketed (if we have that information). If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please email us at privacy@thru-line.com.
7. THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES
a. Links to Third-Party Websites
The Services contains links to other websites operated by schools and other third parties to which we do not control. Even if an affiliation exists between us and such website, that websites may have privacy policies that are very different from this Policy. You should read the privacy policy of every website you visit. While we expect our customers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users, we cannot be responsible for the actions of third parties. The links from this Site do not imply that we endorse or have reviewed these third party sites. We encourage you to consult that website’s privacy policy before providing Your Information to it and whenever interacting with any website.
b. Third-Party Tracking
Third-party social networks that provide interactive plug-ins or social networking features (for example, to allow you to “Like” a page on the Services) on the Services, may use cookies or other methods (for example, web beacons) to gather information regarding your use of our websites and apps. The use of such information by a third party depends on the privacy policy available on that social network’s website, which we encourage you to carefully review. Such third parties may use these cookies or other tracking methods for their own purposes by relating information about your use of the Services with any of Your Information that they may have.
8. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION THROUGH BUSINESS TRANSFERS
As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In connection with a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, we may assign or transfer this Policy and any and all of Your Information to the person or entity acquiring the applicable assets or succeeding to the applicable business. In the event of any such transaction, this Policy shall remain in full force and effect and shall be binding on you and any such successor and/or assign. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors’ rights generally, we may not be able to control how Your Information is treated, transferred, or used.
9. USERS FROM OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES
The Services is hosted in the United States and is governed by United States law. If you are using the Services from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using the Services, you consent to your information being transferred to our facilities and to the facilities of those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy.
10. NO CHILDREN
The Services does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information through the Services. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Policy by instructing their children never to provide personal information on this Site without their permission. Any information we receive from users we believe to be under the age of 13 will be purged from our database.
11. CONTACTING US
If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, please contact us using one of the methods specified below.
privacy@thru-line.com.
Thruline Marketing, Inc.
15500 W. 113th St., Suite 200
Lenexa, KS 66219
Phone: +1.913.254.6000
Search Beauty Schools
Select a ProgramCosmetologyEsthetics and Skin CareNail TechnologyBarberingMake-Up Artist TrainingElectrologyLaser TrainingPermanent Make-UpTeacher TrainingContinuing EducationMassage TherapyHair DesignSalon ManagementHair BraidingFashion Design
Home | Find a School | Beauty & Cosmetology Programs | Beauty School Blog | Resources | Beauty ContestsContact Us | Sitemap | Privacy Policy
